<resources>
    <string name="terms">http://bit.ly/TnCcontactsGame</string>

    <string name="interstitial_ad_sample">Interstitial Ad Sample</string>
    <string name="start_level">Level 1</string>
    <string name="next_level">Next Level</string>
    <!-- -
        This is an ad unit ID for an interstitial test ad. Replace with your own interstitial ad unit id.
        For more information, see https://support.google.com/admob/answer/3052638
    <!- -->
    <!--<string name="interstitial_ad_unit_id">ca-app-pub-3940256099942544/1033173712</string>-->
    <string name="interstitial_ad_unit_id">ca-app-pub-6767332469316331/3960569734</string>


    <string name="app_name">KYN</string>
    <string name="title_activity_welcome">Home Screen</string>
    <string name="next">NEXT</string>
    <string name="skip">SKIP</string>
    <string name="start">Agree</string>
    <string name="slide_1_title">Have you ever wondered in which name your friend saved your contact number in his/her phone? </string>
    <string name="slide_1_desc">This game helps you to find out how your friend saved your name!!</string>
    <string name="slide_2_title">How to find your name?!</string>
    <string name="slide_2_desc">Just enter the mobile number of your friend and hit enter! Hurry! you get the name of you how he/she saved in his/her mobile! \n\n Remember your friend too should have installed this app too to get the result.</string>
    <string name="slide_3_title">How it works?!</string>
    <string name="slide_3_desc">In order to access your friend, your friend also needs to install this game. Once he/she installed then try again you will get the results now! App is 50 to 80% accurate, we are trying our best to get the best.</string>
    <string name="slide_4_title">Caution</string>
    <string name="slide_4_desc">Please read the terms and conditions carefully, this game only uses your contact details. Please provide appropriate permissions. Have fun and Enjoy the Game! </string>
    <string name="play_again_desc">To see the welcome slider again, goto Settings -> apps -> welcome slider -> clear data</string>
    <string name="play_again">Play Again</string>
    <string name="permission_denied_txt">Permission Error.. Please try again..</string>
    <string name="impossible_game">Impossible Game</string>
    <string name="retry_button_text">Retry</string>
    <string name="watch_video_button_text">Watch Video for 10 additional coins</string>
    <string name="default_coin_text">Coins: 0</string>
    <string name="title_activity_inter_ad">InterAdActivity</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="resa">What could be the reason?\n1.Your friend doesnot have your number saved\n2.Your friend doesnot have the app installed\n3. He/She might used different number during OTP verification\n4. Number wrong or Issues with country code. \n thats all...</string>
    <string name="actio">We aware that Ads will annoy you,
        \nbut Ads are the only source of revenue for the backend expenses of the App.
        \nSo kindly bear with us.\n\nWe hope app will give you fun and unique experience
        \nas this is the first app in this kind!!!</string>
    <!-- -
            This is an ad unit ID for an interstitial test ad. Replace with your own interstitial ad unit id.
            For more information, see https://support.google.com/admob/answer/3052638
        <!- -->
    <!--<string name="interstitial_ad_unit_id">ca-app-pub-3940256099942544/1033173712</string>-->
    <string name="termsfull">termsfull</string>
    <!-- <string name="banner_app_id">ca-app-pub-5300816088056407~3900891804</string>
        <string name="banner_unit_id">ca-app-pub-5300816088056407/5335077181</string>-->


    <string name="htmll"><![CDATA[<h1>Terms and conditions</h1>
<p>These terms and conditions are an agreement between Mobile Application Developer.
This Agreement sets forth the general terms and conditions of your use of the Contacts Game mobile application and any of its products or services (collectively, Mobile Application or Services).</p>
<h2>Accounts and membership</h2>
<p>You must be at least 18 years of age to use this Mobile Application. By using this Mobile Application and by agreeing to this Agreement you warrant and represent that you are at least 18 years of age. If you create an account in the Mobile Application, you are responsible for maintaining the security of your account and you are fully responsible for all activities that occur under the account and any other actions taken in connection with it. We may, but have no obligation to, monitor and review new accounts before you may sign in and use our Services. Providing false contact information of any kind may result in the termination of your account. You must immediately notify us of any unauthorized uses of your account or any other breaches of security. We will not be liable for any acts or omissions by you, including any damages of any kind incurred as a result of such acts or omissions.</p>
<h2>User content</h2>
<p>We do not own any data, information or material (Content) that you submit in the Mobile Application in the course of using the Service. You shall have sole responsibility for the accuracy, quality, integrity, legality, reliability, appropriateness, and intellectual property ownership or right to use of all submitted Content. We may, but have no obligation to, monitor and review Content in the Mobile Application submitted or created using our Services by you. Unless specifically permitted by you, your use of the Mobile Application does not grant us the license to use, reproduce, adapt, modify, publish or distribute the Content created by you or stored in your user account for commercial, marketing or any similar purpose. But you grant us permission to access, copy, distribute, store, transmit, reformat, display and perform the Content of your user account solely as required for the purpose of providing the Services to you.</p>
<h2>Backups</h2>
<p>We perform regular backups of the Content and will do our best to ensure completeness and accuracy of these backups. In the event of the hardware failure or data loss we will restore backups automatically to minimize the impact and downtime.</p>
<h2>Links to other mobile applications</h2>
<p>Although this Mobile Application may link to other mobile applications, we are not, directly or indirectly, implying any approval, association, sponsorship, endorsement, or affiliation with any linked mobile application, unless specifically stated herein. Some of the links in the Mobile Application may be affiliate links. This means if you click on the link and purchase an item, Mobile Application Developer will receive an affiliate commission. We are not responsible for examining or evaluating, and we do not warrant the offerings of, any businesses or individuals or the content of their mobile applications. We do not assume any responsibility or liability for the actions, products, services, and content of any other third-parties. You should carefully review the legal statements and other conditions of use of any mobile application which you access through a link from this Mobile Application. Your linking to any other off-site mobile applications is at your own risk.</p>
<h2>Changes and amendments</h2>
<p>We reserve the right to modify this Agreement or its policies relating to the Mobile Application or Services at any time, effective upon posting of an updated version of this Agreement in the Mobile Application. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. Continued use of the Mobile Application after any such changes shall constitute your consent to such changes.</p>
<h2>Acceptance of these terms</h2>
<p>You acknowledge that you have read this Agreement and agree to all its terms and conditions. By using the Mobile Application or its Services you agree to be bound by this Agreement. If you do not agree to abide by the terms of this Agreement, you are not authorized to use or access the Mobile Application and its Services.</p>
<p>and you have been informed and you agree to the following,</p>
<p>You acknowledge that you have read this Agreement and agree to all its terms and conditions. By using the Mobile Application or its Services you agree to be bound by this Agreement. If you do not agree to abide by the terms of this Agreement, you are not authorized to use or access the Mobile Application and its Services.</p>
<p>Both you and your friend has to install this app to get the results.</p>
<p>Your contacts details will be saved to server, and will be available to other users even if you uninstall the app.</p>
<p>Options to delete your data may or may not be added in future app updates.</p>
<p>We do not take any responsibilities on anything happens because of this app. Please use this app on your own risk.</p>
<p>If you do not wish to share your contacts, not encouraged to use the app. It\'s just a fun game. We don\'t take any responsibilities.</p>
<p>If terms and conditions are updated , it will be updated on the website only. please take a look at it.</p>
<p>We gain revenue using Ads in app. in app purchases can be added in future. Kindly bear with us for the Ads.</p>
<p>If you find app useful , please share and support.</p>
<p>If terms and conditions are updated , it will be updated on the website only. please take a look at it.</p>
<p>Results are 50 to 80% accurate only. we try our level best to get the best. If results are not relavant we are unable to do anything. Its just a try. thanks for understanding.</p>
<h2>Contacting us</h2>
<p>If you have any questions about this Agreement, please contact us. also can mail us at apparpattavan@gmail.com</p>
<p>This document was last updated on November 26, 2019</p>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="banner_unit_id">testtestad</string>
    <string name="title_activity_i_stitial_one">MainActivity</string>
</resources>

